hey you guys i am doing a review on this
product which is called a toastmaster
airfryer
okay um this this airfryer is
is i'm telling y'all it's awesome i
rinsed my chicken off i decided i was
going to be a little bit lazy
today and i i'm telling you absolutely
love this product
i went i got some um some chicken out of
my
um refrigerator that was frozen i rinsed
my chicken off
i put it into this air fryer about 10
pieces of chicken look at that
i'm telling y'all this worked this is my
second time
using this product my first time i had
some turkey bacon that i had
put up in here and it cooked it's so
good this is i'm talking about fried
i don't have no flour it's not battered
it is
nothing i'm telling y'all this is like
the healthiest way that you can eat your
your food if you have a larger family
you may want to consider going a little
bit bigger than this
but being that um it's just me and my
two children
um you know i just you know decided to
go ahead and use it and be a little bit
lazy
behind the scenes today but hey um
we got some macaroni to go with it right
there
i had cooked some macaroni getting a
little bit
right there but i took some macaroni to
go with this chicken i'm telling you
guys
this is the bomb okay it's called
toastmaster i got this again from dollar
general
um for approximately twenty dollars
in tax with included was like 25
and i recommend this product okay um tag
toastmaster in this in this uh post but
anyway y'all like comment and subscribe
to this uh youtube channel
like this video i appreciate you guys
viewing my videos my views have went up
and um thank you guys thank you thank
you thank you
hey you guys i just wanted to give you
guys the update on how the
chicken turned out um that i put this
frozen chicken into
um the toastmaster airfryer this is a
good product again to use i do recommend
it thank you all for watching